Hey, welcome back. In this section, we've added so many features to our climbing system.
嘿，欢迎回来。在这一节中，我们为我们的攀登系统增加了许多功能。
And before we move on, there are a couple of issues that I'd like to fix. So first,
而在我们继续前进之前，有几个问题是我想解决的。所以首先、
I'm going to go back to my code. Then I'm going to scroll up to this toggle climbing.
我要回到我的代码中去。然后，我要向上滚动到这个切换攀登。
So I'm going to change the default value for this can climb down ledge. So instead of 300 units,
所以我要改变这个可以爬下壁架的默认值。所以不要用300个单位、
for the second line trace, I'm going to change it to 200 units. Then I'm going to use lab coding
第二行追踪，我要把它改为200单位。然后我将使用实验室编码
again. All right, lab coding succeeded. Now I'm going to climb up. And on a surface like this,
再来一次。好了，实验室编码成功了。现在我要爬上去了。而在这样的一个表面上、
at this moment, that second line trace does not have a hit, so I can climb down.
此刻，第二条线迹没有被击中，所以我可以爬下去。
And I think this works much better than the original way. And another thing that I like to
而且我认为这比原来的方式好得多。还有一件事，我喜欢
fix. So right now, I don't quite like the blending between the montage and this climb locomotion.
修复。所以现在，我不太喜欢蒙太奇和这个爬升运动之间的融合。
And to fix that, I'm going to double click to open this climb down ledge.
为了解决这个问题，我将双击打开这个爬下的壁架。
So I'm going to adjust this blend out time here. Currently, this blend time is 0.25 seconds.
所以我要在这里调整这个混合时间。目前，这个混合时间是0.25秒。
And by lowering down this number here, we'll also be playing more of this original information,
通过降低这里的数字，我们也将播放更多的这个原始信息、
and we can descend our character more. So I'm going to lower down this blend time to 0.24,
我们可以让我们的角色下降得更多。所以我要把这个混合时间降低到0.24、
and change this blend option from linear to cubic and hit save. Back to my level,
并将这个混合选项从线性改为立方，然后点击保存。回到我的水平、
I'm going to test again. So click play and go to this surface, climb up, then try to climb down.
我将再次进行测试。所以点击播放，到这个表面，爬上去，然后试着爬下来。
Yeah, I think this looks a bit better than the original one. I'm going to try again in here.
是的，我认为这看起来比原来的要好一些。我打算在这里再试一次。
A bit smoother, I think.
我觉得更光滑一点。
And that should be all of it. Now we have our climb locomotion ready. We can climb up,
这应该就是全部了。现在我们已经准备好了我们的爬升运动。我们可以往上爬了、
and we can climb down. When we have reached the floor, we can exit the climb state. Great,
也可以往下爬。当我们到达地面时，我们可以退出爬升状态。好极了、
everything is working.
一切都正常了。
And there's one last thing that I want to do. So I'm going to close my project
还有最后一件事，我想做。所以我将关闭我的项目
and go to this tick component. I'm going to come out this function. I don't need to see
并转到这个打勾组件。我将出来这个函数。我不需要再看到
those debug lines anymore. And I'm also going to go inside of it.
那些调试线了。我也要进入它的内部。
And I'm going to go to this button here. And I'm going to go to this button here.
我要去这个按钮那里。我要去这个按钮那里。
我要去这个按钮那里。我要去这个按钮这里。
And I'm also going to go inside of it. And disable these debug lines. So they need to be true.
我也要去它的内部。并禁用这些调试行。所以它们需要为真。
And I'm going to compile. I have a successful compile. And in the next section,
然后我就开始编译了。我有一个成功的编译。在下一节中
we are going to look at how we can add in more interesting features. I'll see you in the next section.
我们将看看如何加入更多有趣的功能。下一节见。